Inventory of the Chiang Kai-shek Diaries
Hoover Institution Archives
- Diaries [Use Copies], 1917-1972
  - 1947
    - April 1947 (Box-folder 46: 7)
    - May 1947 (Box-folder 46: 8)
    - June 1947 (Box-folder 46: 9)
    - July 1947 (Box-folder 46: 10)
    - August 1947 (Box-folder 46: 11)
    - September 1947 (Box-folder 46: 12)
    - October 1947 (Box-folder 46: 13)
    - November 1947 (Box-folder 46: 14)
    - December 1947 (Box-folder 46: 15)
  - 1948
    - General 1948 (Box-folder 46: 16)
    - January 1948 (Box-folder 46: 17)
    - February 1948 (Box-folder 46: 18)
    - March 1948 (Box-folder 46: 19)
    - April 1948 (Box-folder 46: 20)
    - May 1948 (Box-folder 46: 21)
    - June 1948 (Box-folder 47: 1)
    - July 1948 (Box-folder 47: 2)
    - August 1948 (Box-folder 47: 3)
    - September 1948 (Box-folder 47: 4)
    - October 1948 (Box-folder 47: 5)
    - November 1948 (Box-folder 47: 6)
    - December 1948 (Box-folder 47: 7)
  - 1949
    - General 1949 (Box-folder 47: 8)
    - January 1949 (Box-folder 47: 9)
    - February 1949 (Box-folder 47: 10)
    - March 1949 (Box-folder 47: 11)
    - April 1949 (Box-folder 47: 12)
    - May 1949 (Box-folder 47: 13)
    - June 1949 (Box-folder 47: 14)
    - July 1949 (Box-folder 47: 15)
    - August 1949 (Box-folder 47: 16)
    - September 1949 (Box-folder 47: 17)
    - October 1949 (Box-folder 47: 18)
    - November 1949 (Box-folder 47: 19)
    - December 1949 (Box-folder 47: 20)
  - 1950
    - General 1950 (Box-folder 48: 1)
    - January 1950 (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - February 1950 (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - March 1950 (Box-folder 48: 4)
    - April 1950 (Box-folder 48: 5)
    - May 1950 (Box-folder 48: 6)
    - June 1950 (Box-folder 48: 7)
    - July 1950 (Box-folder 48: 8)
    - August 1950 (Box-folder 48: 9)
    - September 1950 (Box-folder 48: 10)
    - October 1950 (Box-folder 48: 11)
    - November 1950 (Box-folder 48: 12)
    - December 1950 (Box-folder 48: 13)
  - 1951
    - General 1951 (Box-folder 48: 14)
    - January 1951 (Box-folder 48: 15)
    - February 1951 (Box-folder 48: 16)
    - March 1951 (Box-folder 48: 17)
    - April 1951 (Box-folder 48: 18)
    - May 1951 (Box-folder 48: 19)
    - June 1951 (Box-folder 49: 1)
    - July 1951 (Box-folder 49: 2)
    - August 1951 (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - September 1951 (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - October 1951 (Box-folder 49: 5)
    - November 1951 (Box-folder 49: 6)
    - December 1951 (Box-folder 49: 7)
  - 1952
    - General 1952 (Box-folder 49: 8)
    - January 1952 (Box-folder 49: 9)
    - February 1952 (Box-folder 49: 10)
    - March 1952 (Box-folder 49: 11)
    - April 1952 (Box-folder 49: 12)
    - May 1952 (Box-folder 49: 13)
    - June 1952 (Box-folder 49: 14)
    - July 1952 (Box-folder 49: 15)
    - August 1952 (Box-folder 49: 16)
    - September 1952 (Box-folder 49: 17)
    - October 1952 (Box-folder 49: 18)
    - November 1952 (Box-folder 49: 19)
    - December 1952 (Box-folder 49: 20)
  - 1953
    - General 1953 (Box-folder 50: 1)
    - January 1953 (Box-folder 50: 2)
    - February 1953 (Box-folder 50: 3)
    - March 1953 (Box-folder 50: 4)
    - April 1953 (Box-folder 50: 5)
    - May 1953 (Box-folder 50: 6)
    - June 1953 (Box-folder 50: 7)
    - July 1953 (Box-folder 50: 8)
    - August 1953 (Box-folder 50: 9)
    - September 1953 (Box-folder 50: 10)
    - October 1953 (Box-folder 50: 11)
    - November 1953 (Box-folder 50: 12)
    - December 1953 (Box-folder 50: 13)
  - 1954
    - General 1954 (Box-folder 50: 14)
    - January 1954 (Box-folder 50: 15)
    - February 1954 (Box-folder 50: 16)
    - March 1954 (Box-folder 50: 17)
    - April 1954 (Box-folder 50: 18)
    - May 1954 (Box-folder 50: 19)
    - June 1954 (Box-folder 50: 20)
    - July 1954 (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - August 1954 (Box-folder 51: 2)
    - September 1954 (Box-folder 51: 3)
    - October 1954 (Box-folder 51: 4)
    - November 1954 (Box-folder 51: 5)
    - December 1954 (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - 1955
    - General 1955 (Box-folder 51: 7)
    - January 1955 (Box-folder 51: 8)
    - February 1955 (Box-folder 51: 9)
    - March 1955 (Box-folder 51: 10)
    - April 1955 (Box-folder 51: 11)
    - May 1955 (Box-folder 51: 12)
    - June 1955 (Box-folder 51: 13)
    - July 1955 (Box-folder 51: 14)
    - August 1955 (Box-folder 51: 15)
    - September 1955 (Box-folder 51: 16)
    - October 1955 (Box-folder 51: 17)
    - November 1955 (Box-folder 51: 18)
    - December 1955 (Box-folder 51: 19)
  - CLOSED (Box 52-64)
  - 1956
    - General 1956 (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - January 1956 (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - February 1956 (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - March 1956 (Box-folder 65: 4)
    - April 1956 (Box-folder 65: 5)
    - May 1956 (Box-folder 65: 6)
    - June 1956 (Box-folder 65: 7)
    - July 1956 (Box-folder 65: 8)
    - August 1956 (Box-folder 65: 9)
    - September 1956 (Box-folder 65: 10)
    - October 1956 (Box-folder 65: 11)
    - November 1956 (Box-folder 65: 12)
    - December 1956 (Box-folder 65: 13)
  - 1957
    - General 1957 (Box-folder 65: 14)
    - January 1957 (Box-folder 65: 15)
    - February 1957 (Box-folder 65: 16)
    - March 1957 (Box-folder 65: 17)
    - April 1957 (Box-folder 66: 1)
    - May 1957 (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - June 1957 (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - July 1957 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - August 1957 (Box-folder 66: 5)
    - September 1957 (Box-folder 66: 6)
    - October 1957 (Box-folder 66: 7)
    - November 1957 (Box-folder 66: 8)
    - December 1957 (Box-folder 66: 9)
  - 1958
    - January 1958 (Box-folder 66: 10)
    - February 1958 (Box-folder 66: 11)
    - March 1958 (Box-folder 66: 12)
    - April 1958 (Box-folder 66: 13)
    - May 1958 (Box-folder 66: 14)
    - June 1958 (Box-folder 66: 15)
    - July 1958 (Box-folder 66: 16)
    - August 1958 (Box-folder 66: 17)
    - September 1958 (Box-folder 66: 18)
    - October 1958 (Box-folder 67: 1)
    - November 1958 (Box-folder 67: 2)
    - December 1958 (Box-folder 67: 3)
  - 1959
    - General 1959 (Box-folder 67: 4)
    - January 1959 (Box-folder 67: 5)
    - February 1959 (Box-folder 67: 6)
    - March 1959 (Box-folder 67: 7)
    - April 1959 (Box-folder 67: 8)
    - May 1959 (Box-folder 67: 9)
    - June 1959 (Box-folder 67: 10)
    - July 1959 (Box-folder 67: 11)
    - August 1959 (Box-folder 67: 12)
    - September 1959 (Box-folder 67: 13)
    - October 1959 (Box-folder 67: 14)
    - November 1959 (Box-folder 67: 15)
    - December 1959 (Box-folder 67: 16)
  - 1960
    - General 1960 (Box-folder 67: 17)
    - January 1960 (Box-folder 67: 18)
    - February 1960 (Box-folder 67: 19)
    - March 1960 (Box-folder 67: 20)
    - April 1960 (Box-folder 67: 21)
    - May 1960 (Box-folder 67: 22)
    - June 1960 (Box-folder 67: 23)
    - July 1960 (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - August 1960 (Box-folder 68: 2)
    - September 1960 (Box-folder 68: 3)
    - October 1960 (Box-folder 68: 4)
    - November 1960 (Box-folder 68: 5)
    - December 1960 (Box-folder 68: 6)
  - 1961
    - General 1961 (Box-folder 68: 7)
    - January 1961 (Box-folder 68: 8)
    - February 1961 (Box-folder 68: 9)
    - March 1961 (Box-folder 68: 10)
    - April 1961 (Box-folder 68: 11)
    - May 1961 (Box-folder 68: 12)
    - June 1961 (Box-folder 68: 13)
    - July 1961 (Box-folder 68: 14)
    - August 1961 (Box-folder 68: 15)
    - September 1961 (Box-folder 68: 16)
    - October 1961 (Box-folder 68: 17)
    - November 1961 (Box-folder 68: 18)
    - December 1961 (Box-folder 68: 19)
  - Sui Yi Shou Lu, 1961
    - General 1961 (Box-folder 68: 20)
    - January-February 1961 (Box-folder 68: 18)
    - March-April 1961 (Box-folder 68: 18)
    - May-June 1961 (Box-folder 69: 1)
    - July-August 1961 (Box-folder 69: 2)
    - September-October 1961 (Box-folder 69: 3)
    - November-December 1961 (Box-folder 69: 4)
    - Reflections: Year in Review (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - 1962
    - General 1962 (Box-folder 69: 6)
    - January 1962 (Box-folder 69: 7)
    - February 1962 (Box-folder 69: 8)
    - March 1962 (Box-folder 69: 9)
    - April 1962 (Box-folder 69: 10)
    - May 1962 (Box-folder 69: 11)
    - June 1962 (Box-folder 69: 12)
    - July 1962 (Box-folder 69: 13)
    - August 1962 (Box-folder 69: 14)
    - September 1962 (Box-folder 69: 15)
    - October 1962 (Box-folder 69: 16)
    - November 1962 (Box-folder 69: 17)
    - December 1962 (Box-folder 69: 18)
  - 1963
    - General 1963 (Box-folder 69: 19)
    - January 1963 (Box-folder 69: 20)
    - February 1963 (Box-folder 70: 1)
    - March 1963 (Box-folder 70: 2)
    - April 1963 (Box-folder 70: 3)
    - May 1963 (Box-folder 70: 4)
    - June 1963 (Box-folder 70: 5)
    - July 1963 (Box-folder 70: 6)
    - August 1963 (Box-folder 70: 7)
    - September 1963 (Box-folder 70: 8)
    - October 1963 (Box-folder 70: 9)
    - November 1963 (Box-folder 70: 10)
    - December 1963 (Box-folder 70: 11)
  - 1964
    - General 1964 (Box-folder 70: 12)
    - January 1964 (Box-folder 70: 13)
    - February 1964 (Box-folder 70: 14)
    - March 1964 (Box-folder 70: 15)
    - April 1964 (Box-folder 70: 16)
    - May 1964 (Box-folder 70: 17)
    - June 1964 (Box-folder 70: 18)
    - July 1964 (Box-folder 71: 1)
    - August 1964 (Box-folder 71: 2)
    - September 1964 (Box-folder 71: 3)
    - October 1964 (Box-folder 71: 4)
    - November 1964 (Box-folder 71: 5)
    - December 1964 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - 1965
    - General 1965 (Box-folder 71: 7)
    - January 1965 (Box-folder 71: 8)
    - February 1965 (Box-folder 71: 9)
    - March 1965 (Box-folder 71: 10)
    - April 1965 (Box-folder 71: 11)
    - May 1965 (Box-folder 71: 12)
    - June 1965 (Box-folder 71: 13)
    - July 1965 (Box-folder 71: 14)
    - August 1965 (Box-folder 72: 1)
    - September 1965 (Box-folder 72: 2)
    - October 1965 (Box-folder 72: 3)
    - November 1965 (Box-folder 72: 4)
    - December 1965 (Box-folder 72: 5)
  - 1966
    - General 1966 (Box-folder 72: 6)
    - January 1966 (Box-folder 72: 7)
    - February 1966 (Box-folder 72: 8)
    - March 1966 (Box-folder 72: 9)
    - April 1966 (Box-folder 72: 10)
    - May 1966 (Box-folder 72: 11)
    - June 1966 (Box-folder 72: 12)
    - July 1966 (Box-folder 72: 13)
    - August 1966 (Box-folder 72: 14)
    - September 1966 (Box-folder 72: 15)
    - October 1966 (Box-folder 72: 16)
    - November 1966 (Box-folder 73: 1)
    - December 1966 (Box-folder 73: 2)
  - 1967
    - January 1967 (Box-folder 73: 3)
    - February 1967 (Box-folder 73: 4)
    - March 1967 (Box-folder 73: 5)
    - April 1967 (Box-folder 73: 6)
    - May 1967 (Box-folder 73: 7)
    - June 1967 (Box-folder 73: 8)
    - July 1967 (Box-folder 73: 9)
    - August 1967 (Box-folder 73: 10)
    - September 1967 (Box-folder 73: 11)
    - October 1967 (Box-folder 73: 12)
    - November 1967 (Box-folder 73: 13)
    - December 1967 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - 1968
    - Volume One 1968
      - General 1968 (Box-folder 74: 2)
      - January 1968 (Box-folder 74: 3)
      - February 1968 (Box-folder 74: 4)
      - March 1968 (Box-folder 74: 5)
      - April 1968 (Box-folder 74: 6)
      - May 1968 (Box-folder 74: 7)
      - June 1968 (Box-folder 74: 8)
      - July 1968 (Box-folder 74: 9)
      - August 1968 (Box-folder 74: 10)
      - September 1968 (Box-folder 74: 11)
      - October 1968 (Box-folder 74: 12)
      - November 1968 (Box-folder 74: 13)
      - December 1968 (Box-folder 74: 14)
    - Volume Two 1968
      - General 1968 (Box-folder 74: 15)
  - 1969
    - General 1969 (Box-folder 74: 16)
    - January 1969 (Box-folder 74: 17)
    - February 1969 (Box-folder 74: 17)
    - March 1969 (Box-folder 75: 1)
    - April 1969 (Box-folder 75: 2)
    - May 1969 (Box-folder 75: 3)
    - June 1969 (Box-folder 75: 4)
    - July 1969 (Box-folder 75: 5)
    - August 1969 (Box-folder 75: 6)
    - September 1969 (Box-folder 75: 7)
    - October 1969 (Box-folder 75: 8)
    - November 1969 (Box-folder 75: 9)
    - December 1969 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - 1970
    - General 1970 (Box-folder 75: 11)
    - January 1970 (Box-folder 75: 12)
    - February 1970 (Box-folder 75: 13)
    - March 1970 (Box-folder 75: 14)
    - April 1970 (Box-folder 75: 15)
    - May 1970 (Box-folder 75: 16)
    - June 1970 (Box-folder 75: 17)
    - July 1970 (Box-folder 75: 18)
    - August 1970 (Box-folder 76: 1)
    - September 1970 (Box-folder 76: 2)
    - October 1970 (Box-folder 76: 3)
    - November 1970 (Box-folder 76: 4)
    - December 1970 (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - 1971
    - General 1971 (Box-folder 76: 6)
    - January 1971 (Box-folder 76: 7)
    - February 1971 (Box-folder 76: 8)
    - March 1971 (Box-folder 76: 9)
    - April 1971 (Box-folder 76: 10)
    - May 1971 (Box-folder 76: 11)
    - June 1971 (Box-folder 76: 12)
    - July 1971 (Box-folder 76: 13)
    - August 1971 (Box-folder 76: 14)
    - September 1971 (Box-folder 76: 15)
    - October 1971 (Box-folder 76: 16)
    - November 1971 (Box-folder 76: 17)
    - December 1971 (Box-folder 76: 18)
  - 1972
    - General 1972 (Box-folder 76: 19)
    - January 1972 (Box-folder 76: 20)
    - February 1972 (Box-folder 76: 21)
    - March 1972 (Box-folder 76: 22)
    - April 1972 (Box-folder 76: 23)
    - May 1972 (Box-folder 76: 24)
    - June 1972 (Box-folder 76: 25)
    - July 1972 (Box-folder 76: 26)